speakspeak.com 2011-11-10

# Speakspeak: About Us: Privacy Policy

Speakspeak is committed to user privacy in our products and services. This policy outlines our personal information handling practices. If you give us personal information, we will treat it according to this policy. 

This policy covers Speakspeak's corporate web sites. 

Speakspeak encourages you to read this privacy policy and those of all web sites you visit.  

### Types and uses of personal information.

Your personal information is used in the following ways:   
**User IDs and Passwords**. Provides you with access to your profile areas and to protected content.   
**Account Information**. These tell us more about who you are, how to contact you, and your billing information. Also contains any preferences you have provided, such as language, email format and interests.   
**Email Correspondence**. Used to raise and respond to issues and inquiries of all types. Also used to distribute information about Speakspeak, our products, and services.   
**Transactions**. Shows which products and services you have requested.   
We will only use your personal information in the ways specified when it was collected. We will not subsequently change the way in which we use your personal information, unless you consent to the new usage. 

### Security measures

We protect the personal information you share with us. Access to your personal information is limited to people who need it to do their job. 

Authorized third party agents may also need access to some of your personal information. We only provide third party agents with the minimum amount of information needed to complete the requested service or transaction. We do not otherwise share your personal information with third parties, unless you have granted us permission to do so. 

### Data Retention

Speakspeak will not retain your personal information longer than is necessary for the purposes for which it was collected. 

### Linked web sites

We sometimes provide links to third party sites. Since we do not control these Web sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) third party sites. 

### Children's privacy

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems. 

### Cookies

The Speakspeak Web site uses cookies. Cookies help us provide a better user experience by storing your quiz and test scores. Speakspeak also uses cookies when you register for a course. In this situation, a cookie will store useful information that enables our Web site to remember you when you return. Speakspeak can only read cookies from Speakspeak Web sites. 

If you choose to disable cookies in your browser, you can still access our Web site, but some functionality may not work as expected. 

### Accessing and updating information

We need your help in making sure your personal information is correct in our systems. Please notify us of changes to your name, address, title, phone number or email address. 

### Unsubscribing

Each email newsletter has instructions on how to unsubscribe.
